Guide to the Evarts Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Jeremiah Evarts, 1798-1833; Series I; 28.75 linear feet (51 boxes)
  - Personal, Legal, and Financial Papers
    - Property estimates, 1810 June 1-1816 January 1 1817 January 1-1824 December 31 (Box 6, Folder 210-211)
    - Bills and receipts, 1810-1811, 1815-1818, [1819?], 1821, undated, 1823-1830 (Box 6, Folder 212-218)
    - Bills and receipts (including "cash book"), 1831 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Account book of Jeremiah Evarts, Branch Bank of Boston, 1817-1821 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - Account book (principally the account of James Evarts [father] to Jeremiah Evarts), 1830 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - Account books of expenses, Mehetabel S. Evarts, 1831, 1832, undated (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - List of books, "sent to Mr. Armstrong to be sold at the annexed price", undated (Box 7, Folder 223)
- William Maxwell Evarts, 1830-1901; Series II; 14.75 linear feet (36 boxes)
  Series II, "William Maxwell Evarts," has been divided into five subsections:
  a) correspondence
  b) legal papers
  c) Congressional papers
  d) memorabilia
  e) financial records
  The correspondence contains letters to and from William Maxwell Evarts, grouped together and arranged alphabetically by correspondent. A letterbook (1889 Dec 17 - 1891 Mar 19), containing copies of letters written by Evarts in that period, precedes the alphabetized letters received. At the end of the correspondence are two folders of unidentified letters, letters of congratulations, and letters not written or received by Evarts. Some of the letters of congratulations sent to Evarts on his election to the United States Senate and on his golden wedding anniversary were written by individuals whose names also appear in the alphabetized correspondence.
  The legal papers consist of briefs, transcripts, memoranda, and opinions. There are several folders of opinions by William Maxwell Evarts and others, arranged chronologically. Additional opinions may be found with the case material. The case material is arranged alphabetically by the name of the case or subject. In certain instances, a series of related cases has been grouped together for the sake of convenience under the general name by which they were known, e. g., Alabama claims, bank tax cases. (It was not possible to determine in all instances whether case material was with Evarts' papers because he had been retained as counsel, consulted for an opinion, or because it had been used for legal reference.) Letters found with the legal papers have been removed and filed in William M. Evarts' general correspondence. However, lists of correspondents whose letters were removed have been placed with the appropriate legislative or judicial proceedings.
  In Congressional papers, memorabilia, and financial records, items have been arranged by type, then filed chronologically.
  - Correspondence
    - Letterbook of William Maxwell Evarts, 1889 December 17-1891 March 19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Acton, Thomas C., and Vanderpoel, A. J., 1883 April 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Letters To WME/From WME:1
    - Adams, F. C., 1881 January 21 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Henry, Undated, n.y. June 12 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Letters To WME/From WME:2
    - Africa, J. Simpson, 1880 March 19 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Alden,(Mrs.)A. L., 1881 January 28 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Alexander, Charles Beatty, 1885 August 18 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Allen, Carrie L., 1885 March 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Alliance Life and Fire Assurance Office (Box 8, Folder 6)
      See: box 12, folder 234
    - Allison, William Boyd, 1882 April 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Alvord, Benjamin, 1880 April 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Amberg, William A., 1881 April 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - American Committee of the Statue of Liberty, William Maxwell Evarts, chairman, 1880-1895 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Letters To WME/From WME:ca. 10/3
    - Andrews, Elisha Whittelsey, 1875 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Letters To WME/From WME:3
    - Andrus, Byron, 1885 March 30 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Angell, James Burrill, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Letters To WME/From WME:4
    - Appleton, Daniel (architectural plans for Windsor, Vermont, estate), 1876, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Appleton, Nathan (Box 8, Folder 11)
      See: box 8, folder 8
    - Arkell, James, 1885 March 12 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Arkell, W. J., and Harrison, Russell B., Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1890 October 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Letters To WME/From WME:1/1
    - Arnold, D. M., 1886 December 9 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Arthur, Chester Alan, 1865 November 18 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Aruba Island Gold Mining Company, 1881, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Aspinwall, Lloyd, 1875 February 20 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/1
    - Astor, John Jacob, 1879 May 8 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Atkinson, Henry M., 1880 March 9 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ayres, William Orville, 1879 May 26 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Bacon, William J., 1879 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Baird, Spencer F., 1886 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Baker, Voorhis and Company, law booksellers and publishers, 1880 September 17 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Baldwin, Truman H., 1872 December 20 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Balestier, J. N., 1857 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Ballinger, R. H., 1884 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Baltimore: Young Men's Republican Club, 1896 March 9 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Bancroft, George, 1879-1881, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
      Letters To WME/From WME:5
    - Bangs, Francis N., 1884 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Barker, Wharton, 1893 June (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Barlow, Bradley (D. W. Dixon, secretary), 1880 February 18 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Barmore, Charles, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      Letters To WME/From WME:6
    - Barnes, Daniel (nephew), 1880 October 16 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Barnett, T. J., 1880, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Bartlett, S(idney?), 1880 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Batchelder, William, 1881, 1884 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Bates, Frances Chapman, 1872-1898 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Barsoll, B. C., 1880 November 17 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Barstow, Caleb, 1870 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Beaman, Charles Coatesworth (son-in- law) (includes letters from Japan in the spring of 1896), 1878-1896 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      Letters To WME/From WME:14
    - Beaman, Hettie Sherman (Evarts) (daughter), 1899 August 29 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Beaman, Helen Wardner; Beaman, Margaret; Beaman, Mary Stacy; Beaman, William Evarts (grandchildren), 1885-1899 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Beckwith, N. M., (1864?) (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Beecher, Henry Ward, 1879 October 10, December 5 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Beeckman, H. G., 1873 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Beers, William A., 1883 November 17 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Belcher, E. W. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Bell, Clark, 1881 February 10 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Bellows, Henry, 1880 February 16 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Belmont, August, 1881 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Benjamin, Park, n.y. May 15 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Benjamin, William Evarts, 1879 December 9 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Bennett, C. E., 1890 December 8 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bennett, Henry S., 1866 June 12 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Berryman, W. H., 1880 November 9 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bestow, Marcus P., 1879 December 4 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bey, Grégoire Aristarchi, 1881 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Bigelow, John (in re: the Rappahannock ), 1864 January 16 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Bile, Carl Steen Andersen de, 1881 March 4 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Billings, Frederick, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Billings, F. N., undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Bingham, S. D., 1880 September 10 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Bishop, Eleanor Fletcher, 1891 May (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Bismarck, Otto, Prince von, 1881 February 14 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Blackford, Eugene G., 1886 March 19 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Blaine, James Gillespie, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Letters To WME/From WME:4/4
    - Blatchford, Samuel, 1863 November 28 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Bloom, Nathaniel, 1882 March 30 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Boardman, Eleanor Sherman, 1880 February 7 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Boardman, Sarah Elizabeth, 1893 September 30 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Boardman, Samuel W., 1880 September 10, 1889 December 7 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Bonaparte, Caroline, 1881 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Boston Civil Service Reform Association, 1890 December 20 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Boston Public Latin School, Moses Merrill, 1895, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Boston Water Works, Gorham P. Low, Jr., 1876 October 14 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Boutell, L. H., 1879 August 5 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Boutelle, Charles Addison, 1885 March 19 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Boynton, Edward C., 1880 August 24 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Bradley, C. S., 1862 December 10 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Brady, John R., 1879, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Brady, Thomas J., 1879 July 25 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Brainerd, Cephas, 1879, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - B(raman?), W. W., 1879 November 15 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Brewster, Benjamin Harris, 1881 December 29 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Brooklyn Daily Times, J. Peters and George H. Fisher, 1879 November 24 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Brown, Amos, 1870 January 4 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Brown, Mrs. Andrew W., 1897 April 2 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Brown, Edward F., 1881 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Brown, Sevellon A., 1882 April 20 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Browne, Edward B. M., 1881 January 29 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - B(ruen?), Mrs. M. A. O., 1863 July 6, 1883 July 2 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Bryce, Lloyd, 1891 April 17 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Buck, Leffert L., 1890 December 15 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Buck, (R. P.) and Company, 1858-1859 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Bundy, Jonas Mills, 1880 October 28 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Burleson, John H., 1879-1880 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Burnham, Ormsby and Company (Box 9, Folder 68)
      See: box 13, folder 292
    - Burnam, C. F., 1880 March 9 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Burnett, Ward B., 1879 August 3 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Burr, Charles Stedman, 1889 August 14 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Butler, E. A., 1880 November 26 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Butler, Louisa C., n.y. December 27 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Butler, Stillman, and Hubbard (Box 9, Folder 69)
      See: box 12, folder 207
    - Camacho, Simon, 1881 February 18 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Camp, B. F., 1879 December 18 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Campbell, (D?) Forbes, 1881 November 2 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Campbell, George Douglas, duke of Argyll, 1864 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Cannon, (D. G. B.?), 1895 July 4 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Cardozo, Michael S., 1876 April 17 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Carmick, E. H., 1881 February 3 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Carpenter, Caroline (in re: claims of Matthew H. Carpenter against Florida Central and Western Railroad), 1882-1883 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      Letters To WME/From WME:13
    - Catlin, E. G., 1881 November 26 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Catlin, J. L., 1879 November 28 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Chamberlin, Daniel H., 1884 May 8 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Chambers, William H., 1880-1881 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Chase, Amos, 1889 April 2 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Chase, George K., 1880, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Chittenden, S. B., 1880 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Choate, Joseph Hodges, 1876-1895 (Box 9, Folder 80)
      Letters To WME/From WME:8
    - Churchill, John C., 1886 January 29 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Churchill, Samuel, 1887 January 7 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Claflin, Horace B., 1879 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Clark, Emmons, 1886 April 26 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Clarke, J. Edwards, 1891 February 12 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Claughton, H. O., 1886 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Cleveland, Sarah P., 1880 July 8 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cleveland, Treadwell, 1872, 1893 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cleveland, W., 1880 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cluss, Adolf, 1879 December 15 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Cobden, Richard, 1864 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Coit, Henry A.; Cole, A. N.; and Coleman, J., 1878, 1880, 1883, 1888 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Colfax, Schuyler, 1884 November 16 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Collier, M. Dwight (in re: report of alumni corporators of Yale College), 1884 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - C(omly?), James M., 1881 January 17 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Cone, A. Cleveland, 1864 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Cone, Mary E. Thropp, 1880 June 14 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Conlin, James, 1899 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Consolidation Coal Company of Maryland, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Coudert, Frederic René, 1880 May 5 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Cowles, William, 1880 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Cox, Christopher C., 1879 June 10 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Cox, James R., 1857-1858 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Cranworth, Robert Monsey Rolfe, baron, 1864 February 19, 1865 June 23 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Crawford, Francis Marion, 1882 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Crawford, T. C., 1890 December 26 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Crilly, George, 1887 September 2 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Crocker and Brewster, 1881 November 25 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Crocker, Ferdinand A., 1885 (Box 9, Folder 97)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/2
    - Croghan, John, 1879 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Crosly, Allen H. (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Curry, Jabez L. M., 1895, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Curtis, F. B. D. (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Curtis, George William, 1880-1885 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Curtis, H. P., 1881 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Cutler, P. Y., 1849 June 21 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Daggett, Albert, 1879-1880 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Dana, Richard Henry, 1879, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Davenport, I. M., 1879 Nov, 18 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Davenport, J. G., 1880 February 13 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Davenport, Mary Morris, undated (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Davis, J. C. B. (Box 10, Folder 103)
      See: box 12, folders 214-216
    - Davis, John, 1882 August 22 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Dayton, Isaac, 1879 November 22 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Deeves, William B., 1895 November 14 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - DeKay, Sidney, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Delafield, Louis L., 1881 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Delano, Lucia M., 1879 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Demarest, William E., 1891 February 11 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Demorest, W. Jennings, 1882 April 5 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Dent, J., 1880 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Develin, John E., 1863 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Dexter, Franklin B., 1889 May 30 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Dickinson, Platt K., 1886 January 9 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Dike, Samuel W., 1895 July 30 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Dilke, Charles W. (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Dillard, W. W., 1894 February 5 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Dittenhoefer, A. J., 1886 July 24 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Dix, Warren Rogers, 1891 March 31 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Doane, William Croswell, 1894 January 26 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Dodd, Mead and Company, E. J. Barnes, 1891 January 12 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Dolan, John, 1879 September 10 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Douglas, Thomas, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Downing, George T., 1879, 1884 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Drake, Mrs. C. C., n.y. October 12 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Draper, Simeon, 1852 February 18 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Drummond, Victor A. W., 1880, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Duffield, George, 1885 January 26 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Duffy, Edward, 1881 February 12 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Duganne, A. J. H., 1888 December 20 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Duncan, A., 1864 February 15 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Duncan, W. B., 1894 March 26 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Dupré, L. J., 1880 December 9 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Durst, John, 1885 March 24 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1895 June 9 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - D'Wolf, William B., 1861 May 28 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Dyett, Anthony R., 1876 March 27 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Eason, J. R. (in re: Mexican claims), 1882 March 6 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Eaton, William Wallace (and James Phelps, John Turner Wait, and Joseph Roswell Hawley, introducing Mr. Reynolds), 1880 June 12 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Edes, M., 1879 May 28 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Edins, A. B., 1881 February (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Edminister, Mrs. James N., 1879 May 19 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Edmunds, George Franklin, 1881, 1883 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Edmunds, Susan M., n.y. May 18 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Edwards, Jonathan, 1882 March 14 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Elkins, George B., 1874, 1876 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Ellingwood, N. Dane, 1874, 1876 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Erlaner, (Baron d'?), 1881 May 29 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Estey, E. S., 1885 January 22 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Estey, Jacob, 1880 October 19 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Evarts, Allen Wardner (son), 1880-1881 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      Letters To WME/From WME:10
    - Evarts, Charles Butler (son), 1848, 1850, 1864, 1875, 1880, 1882, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      Letters To WME/From WME:6/5
    - Evarts, Charles Butler (letters of sympathy on his death), 1891 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Evarts, Emily Charlotte (Potter) (daughter-in-law, Mrs. Prescott Evarts), 1898 December 27 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Evarts, Frederick M., 1882 March 13 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      Letters To WME/From WME:38718
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1844-1849 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/14
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1850-1857 (Box 10, Folder 132)
      Letters To WME/From WME:3/11
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1872 March-April (Box 10, Folder 133)
      Letters To WME/From WME:15
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1872 May (Box 10, Folder 134)
      Letters To WME/From WME:23
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1872 June-December (Box 10, Folder 135)
      Letters To WME/From WME:12
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1878-1880 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      Letters To WME/From WME:2/13
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), 1881, 1885-1888 (Box 10, Folder 137)
      Letters To WME/From WME:1/10
    - Evarts, Helen Minerva (Wardner) (wife), undated (Box 10, Folder 138)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/5
    - Evarts, John Jay (brother), 1828-1829 (Box 10, Folder 139)
      Letters To WME/From WME:0/6
    - Evarts, Maxwell (son), 1888-1895 (Box 10, Folder 140)
      Letters To WME/From WME:7
    - Evarts, Prescott (son), 1890-1898 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - Evarts, Sherman (son), 1880-1881, 1890, 1892, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 142)
      Letters To WME/From WME:9/1
    - Evarts, William (son), 1874 December 10 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Evarts, William Maxwell (grandson), 1895, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Everett, Horace, 1886 September 1 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Eversley, George John Shaw-Lefevre, 1864 (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - Everts, Stephen H., 1884 February 8 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Fallon, Christopher, 1895 June 4 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Farrell, John, 1880-1884 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Farrington, William M., 1881 December 16 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Farwell, John L., 1883 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Feeney, James L., 1885 October 24 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Field, Cyrus West, 1864, 1869, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 149)
      Letters To WME/From WME:4/1
    - Field, Stephen Johnson, 1885 February 19 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Fish, Hamilton, 1882 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Fish, Hamilton, Jr., 1885 January 20 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Fish, H. W., 1880 September 9 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Fish, Julia K., 1881 October 10 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Fisher, George H., 1881 January 16 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Fisher, George P., 1882 April 4 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Fithian, Freeman J., 1879 November 21 (Box 11, Folder 153)
    - Folger, Charles J., 1882 October 17 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Foot, Robert E., 1879 November 15 (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Forbes, John M., 1881, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Forster, George H., 1879, 1881 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Forster, William Edward, 1864 March 4 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Foster, Benjamin B., 1880 June 8 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Francis, John M., 1891 January 21 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - French, Henry F., 1880, 1885 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Frelinghuysen, Frederick T. (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Fuller, Melville W., 1897 October 6 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Funk and Wagnalls, The Voice, 1885 March 11 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Gardiner, David S., 1869 May 31 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Gardiner, Thomas A., 1874 November 11 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Garfield, James A., 1880 September 21 (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Garfield Memorial Hospital, 1881 November 30 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Garland, Augustus Hill, 1880 September 17 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Garner, Laura B., 1895 June 16 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Garrison, Malachi, 1885 February 24 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Geoghegan, Ellen, 1869-1870 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Gibbs, Frederick Waymouth, -1864 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Gifford, George, 1881-1882 (Box 11, Folder 169)
    - Gilbert, J. W., n.y. February 17 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Gilman, Fanny I. R., 1879 November 9 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Goodrich, William W., 1879 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Goward, Gustavus, 1880-1881 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Grace, William H., 1880 January 19 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Grafton, Virginia A., 1885 January 20 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Grant, Ezra, 1879 June 4 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Grant, Ulysses Simpson, 1895 June 18 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Gray, Horace, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Gray, Lewis F., 1881 February 28 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Greene, Daniel Crosby (nephew), 1881 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Greene, Henry Hill (nephew), 1895-1897 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Greene, Jeremiah Evarts (nephew), 1893 September 2 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Greene, John M., 1882 April 18 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Greene, (N?), 1862 March 8 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Greene, Roger Sherman (nephew), 1880 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Gunn, D. G., 1884 November 25 (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Gunnell, Francis M., 1879-1880 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Gunnell, I. S., 1879 November 12 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Guthrie, William D., n.y. February 7 (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - Hadley, Arthur Twining, 1883 February 10 (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - Halderman, John A., 1884 December 24 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Halstead, E. P., 1880 September 7 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Hamilton, John C., 1880 September 30 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Hand, C. A., 1873 December 4 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Hamilton, Schuyler (Box 11, Folder 183)
      See: box 35, folder 668
    - Harcourt, Sir William George Granville Venables Vernon, 1864 (Box 11, Folder 184)
    - Harman, J. W., 1879 November 17 (Box 11, Folder 185)
    - Harper and Brothers, G. G. Conant, 1884 January 17 (Box 11, Folder 185)
    - Harrington, A. E., 1883 (Box 11, Folder 186)
    - Harris, A. W., 1881 January 23 (Box 11, Folder 186)
    - Harrison, Benjamin, 1891 December 14 (Box 11, Folder 187)
    - Hart, William H. H., 1887-1892 (Box 11, Folder 188)
      Letters To WME/From WME:9/2
    - Hart, William H. H., 1892-1897, undated (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - Haskell, Charles C., 1895 October 26 (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - Haswell, Charles H., 1879 June 3 (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - Hawley, Joseph R. (Box 11, Folder 190)
      See: box 10, folder 120
    - Hay, John, 1880, 1888 (Box 11, Folder 191)
      Letters To WME/From WME:9
    - Hayes, Rutherford Birchard telegrams, 1878, 1880 (Box 11, Folder 192)
    - ALS, 1881 March 31 (Box 11, Folder 192)
    - Helper, H. R., 1883 April 5 (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Heney, James B., 1872 August 13 (Box 11, Folder 193)